<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Shenal Silva's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://shenal.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://shenal.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-10T11:45:51+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://shenal.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shenal Silva]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with GSoC 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://shenal.github.io/blog/2013/12/26/getting-started-with-gsoc-2014/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-26T09:59:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://shenal.github.io/blog/2013/12/26/getting-started-with-gsoc-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>GSoC</h3>

<p>I didnt know about GSoC until I was halfway through my first year. It was only after reading Ramidu ayya blog which made me realise that anyone can work for google (even though indirectly). Then upon reading a few more articles on the web I got to know the details of the Summer of Code program.
I wasn&rsquo;t following a particular open source project back in early 2013, therefore couldnt do anything for the 9th GSoC.I was determined after a few people that I know got their projects accepted and i was happy for them.</p>

<p>Work for GSoC 2014 started back in September, with an initative of a few past participants in our university to mentor to be candidates of the program. I too was assigned a mentor, and its been of great help.</p>

<p>Hoping to make a big impact this time.
Cheers!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ozymandiaz]]></title>
    <link href="http://shenal.github.io/blog/2013/08/05/ozymandiaz/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-05T00:57:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://shenal.github.io/blog/2013/08/05/ozymandiaz</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I met a traveller from an antique land<br/>
Who said: Two vast and trunkless legs of stone<br/>
Stand in the desart. Near them, on the sand,</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Half sunk, a shattered visage lies, whose frown,<br/>
And wrinkled lip, and sneer of cold command,<br/>
Tell that its sculptor well those passions read<br/>
Which yet survive, stamped on these lifeless things,<br/>
The hand that mocked them and the heart that fed:<br/>
And on the pedestal these words appear:<br/>
“My name is Ozymandias, king of kings:<br/>
Look on my works, ye Mighty, and despair!”<br/>
Nothing beside remains. Round the decay<br/>
Of that colossal wreck, boundless and bare<br/>
The lone and level sands stretch far away</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
